[Music]
so
if you don't do it
somebody else will
[Music]
[Applause]
as soon as i wake up basically after i
do all you know the regular morning
stuff i come to the markets and look for
any active traits uh as we recorded this
video i actually got into a position um
pretty simple projection level of
support and resistance obviously right
now we're on the one hour time frame if
i were to go over to like the four hour
you guys can see
the simple shifter structure re-tested
the ema sells so we're literally
just barely in profit and we're
currently up right now
about
um this trade could easily make me if it
hits my final take profit thirty forty
thousand so um let's see kind of how
this trade goes throughout the whole
entire day but yeah so far already gotta
trade and now i'm gonna hop on a webinar
with uh all of my students from my
bootcamp and um i'm gonna update the
signal group soon on my app when this
trade hits tp1 i haven't told you guys
the time that i'm going to be doing the
webinar i haven't updated them i'm
simply just going to drop the zoom code
right now and let's see how many people
get on
so here it goes three two
all right let's see
this is um
currently right now
i haven't spoke about this a lot
before
where's my shirt no shirt today we are
headed to the gym after this here is
exactly where we are
right here if you guys notice it's the
exact same play i've already just come
and put this movement all right so we
just finished our webinar right now um
trade is right around the same area we
were up about 4300 earlier and now we're
about 40 200. um basically same thing
price really hasn't moved much uh
hopefully the momentum keeps going
throughout new york and then they're in
london the trade pushes towards my take
profit we got eric pulling up my barber
because i'm looking rough i haven't
gotten a haircut in like seven eight
days i get a haircut every five days
gotta stay looking fresh so um we're
gonna go get a haircut and after that
we're gonna go to uh the hq
[Music]
i was thinking of doing the heart i
wanted to do the heart let's do it
should i do it like a broken heart yeah
that's the same way you did a hand okay
like a pair of nuts or something you
know
what can you do the level of diamond
damn
show me
all right so we just
tried eric to see if we could do the the
level of diamond
i trust you bro let's do it all right
don't show me let me see oh [__]
no pressure
let's face this one
it's just good let's
[Music]
thank you my brother appreciate it
all right so we just getting a freshie i
was looking rough we got our level up
logo so i like switching it up every
single time you know you got to get a
different design um we're gonna go eat
now probably carrot carrot probably
carrot something like healthy i don't
really like i don't like eating anything
unhealthy i don't know it doesn't feel
good in my stomach
um and then after we eat we're gonna
head over to the hq so you guys check it
out see you guys
[Music]
let's go
all right what car uh what do you want
to take like what's better for you to
film you want to take the mclaren or the
rose um
the rose yeah people are going to hate
me though yeah i know nah but we'll take
it out later tonight that's [__]
it is not this is the [__] honestly but
yeah so i usually come to carrot i get
my uh my daily acai without my eyesight
without this the trades will take profit
so you definitely gotta get this on the
daily so
fine
first one at the office today
so this is our level up hq um
kind of like a working progress right
now this is kind of like our hangout
spot uh we uh recently just put up
certificates of our funded traders we're
missing like half of the wall but i'm
like scared of heights so i didn't
finish doing the rest of the wall and
it's like pretty hard to do everything
in line
um
we got a little ping pong table kind of
like our hangout area we just like
messed around a little bit we got a
couch so we went to like get the couch
we told like the person like bro we need
your guys biggest couch so we ended up
getting two and then we put them
together um we're still missing some
things here we actually need um an
artist so we were gonna hire an artist
to come and then paint a bear
like 20 foot tall bear and like a 20
foot long bull and then kind of make
them like fight each other but the
person like flicked or whatever so if
any of you guys are artists and you guys
want to come to the level of hq paint
some things pull up you know you guys
could be as creative as you guys want
um we have
rose sto
exhaust
so we originally got this carpet because
it was gonna like supposed to fill up
everything but yeah clearly it uh
it didn't do anything so we got
obviously the four tvs that we haven't
aligned yet we gotta wait for our guys
to unline them
this is like our spot we got our dinner
table with no chairs but there's one
here yeah well there's only one chair
shout out to baga we're getting the
chair
thanks bro yeah we eat what we just eat
standing up
this is the work in progress um these
are our neighbors the owner of this
liquor uh white gold shout out to these
guys because they're dope as [__] um
tastes really good i'm not a big fan of
coconut water but they like a mix of
like rum and coconut water and they just
hook us up all the time let me show you
guys what we have planned up upstairs
so this is usually like where we meet we
make some content for you guys for level
up and i usually probably spend out of
my day
either like two three hours in here um
we're gonna do like some trading setups
downstairs and then some trading setups
upstairs folks there
so up here we're gonna make this like
our like executive area we're gonna have
a little sofa on this end here um and
then we're going to have like trading
setups all throughout here so it's going
to be like a little private area are we
going to have a short ball uh no
stripper point here not yet maybe up
here just for the executive area because
there's no way you get like a 35 long
like stripper ball like
um so yeah i mean we have uh we're
literally building this you know as our
hangout spot um it's just fun it's
literally the level up hq we have a lot
of things coming in the future here it's
kind of like phase one it's kind of it's
a little bit empty right now because you
probably got it like well like a month
ago
maybe like like a month ago so it's like
a work in progress but um this is
usually where we meet maybe for like two
three hours out of the day and we kind
of brainstorm and we work on anything
related to level up or anything of our
other businesses so this is the spot
where a lot of a lot of crazy innovative
ideas come
from this spot so we're gonna do like a
little meet and greet here with all of
you guys very soon so make sure to check
out the gram so you guys stay tuned
to um whatever events we're gonna have
here privately just for the level of
team so uh stay tuned for that so now
we're gonna chill we're gonna wait for
the guys to get here nobody's here i'm
the first guy at the office today we'll
probably meet for like two three hours
and after that we're gonna head uh to
the gym because it's uh
time to get big
[Music]
we'll be in there for like two three
hours at a time wouldn't you know like
what time it is because of the sun so
now we're gonna
get ready and head to the gym and get
into a nice workout
[Music]
what it do so i'm updating i almost
forgot so the trade that we had running
earlier um basically closed right now
about four or five thousand in profit
market is freezing uh the market closed
so i just updated everybody in the
signal group um if you guys don't know i
have an app my free app this is
basically where i send all of my signals
where i send um free trade alerts it's
literally free in the apple store just
search off the swing trading lab on the
apple google play store it gets
downloaded for free i host a free zoom
in there every single week and
um on september 1st so about like a week
and a half from now i'm going to be
hosting a free webinar and i'm going to
be giving away a prize to anybody that
hops on that zoom call on september 1st
the only way to enter that zunka will be
in the app i'm going to be dropping the
zoom link inside the app on my home page
as you guys can see there's a home page
signal position size calculator a bunch
of stuff um
so now after this i'm gonna go home
shower take a nap and then you know get
a little bit of rest so i can trade
throughout london again
um so if you guys want to be part of
that webinar and part of winning that
giveaway make sure to download the app
swing trading lab on the google and
apple play store and i'll see you guys
at the crib
[__] the tiger
brother fire workout
let's go eat like a burger or something
because
you gotta get fat again cause that's too
much cardio for me bro
luckily we don't have to walk that much
we got parking
right across the street
[Music]
so after my nap i usually come down to
the charts and i analyze basically what
i'm going to be looking for
for the market for london um lately i've
been kind of killing the majority of my
trades in london i've been finding
great success in it and that's like
where i will got in my 13 week winning
streak i've never had a wing streak so
long i used to never really you know
like trade on london but i've been
finding some nice like impulsive move
not the swing trades that i usually do
but there are the trades that have been
hitting for one to three one to four
risk to reward so um i'm gonna drop a
zoom now with the guys and do like a
little market analysis and then after
i'm just gonna throw on a podcast and
just kind of stay up uh while the trades
kind of pull up you know because they're
not it's happened to me before rather
than just like lay back in the chair and
i'll knock out so i'll put on a podcast
or just watch some youtube videos like
some educational stuff while i wait for
the trades to uh to line up
so after like 2-3 hours of waiting in
the markets there's literally nothing um
is where i tell the signal group
basically guys there's literally no
trades that are worth the risk
um so we come back you know they're in
new york so this is why we trade both
systems is why we trade new york and
london we don't get any trades during
london we usually get ones during new
york and i rather not send the trade out
at all versus sending out a bad trade
obviously i only send trades that are
worth the risk
um but you guys can tell by my life like
literally my whole entire day revolves
around trading my business and my health
and if you don't do it somebody else
says you gotta let today be the start
everybody tomorrow consistency is key
and um
we'll see you know what happens now in
new york literally what i do tomorrow is
just repeat this is what a weekday in my
life looks like so if you guys want to
see what a weekend in my life looks like
which it's a lot different from a
weekday for sure uh make sure to drop a
comment below but this is kind of what
you know my trader lifestyle is so um
appreciate you guys watching the video
and let today be the start i'll be
better tomorrow see you guys
[Music]